speedposttrack.in 2017-08-19

# Privacy Policy | SpeedPost Tracking

### speedposttrack.in Privacy Policy

speedposttrack.in has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. This privacy policy is valid only for CurrencyConverterRate.com. This Web site has links to other Web sites which each have their own unique privacy policy. 

### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We also use your IP address to help us identify hackers and others who misuse this website. In this way, we can protect you and other users, and prevent lost business that may result from hackers' activity. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information so that we may better serve you and the community. This information is used at the server level, with the server recognizing the IP address and not the individual person.

### Information Provided by the User

In our contact form and mailing list signup, you may voluntarily submit your name and/or e-mail address. We will use this information only to e-mail you with a response to your questions or to send you the newsletter that you have chosen to receive. We will never share your e-mail address with a third party, nor will we use your e-mail address for any other purpose.

### Site Statistics

Our uses Google Analytics which is a website analytics service provided by Google Inc. When you use this website, the cookie will collect data about your use of the website, and then transmitted to Google servers of American. Google don't publish your IP address on any activities by Google. If you using this website, you tolerate Google collect your personal information to do all of above mentioned.

### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Customer information is stored on a secured server with password security. The servers themselves are stored in a facility featuring 24 hour video surveillance which requires a pass-code to enter. Nightly backups are made of all data and activity on the servers is tracked and recorded.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us here. 

Speedpost services are avaiblae in all popular Indian Cities like Kolkata, Hyderabad, Patna, Nagpur, Chennai, Bangalore, Mumbai, Delhi, Lucknow, Jaipur, Pondicherry, Allahabad, Ahmadabad, Amritsar, Bhopal, Bhubaneswar Calcutta, Calicut Chandigarh, Cochin, Pune, Noida, Trivandrum, Madurai, Trichy, Gurgaon and other cities as well.

##### _** This is not official IndiaPost website _[ www.indiapost.gov.in ]_. All trademarts and copyrights belongs to respective owner._
